{
  "questions" : [

    {
      "question":"She was a devoted wife and looked .... her husband.",
      "options":[
        "at",
        "upon",
        "after"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Good sleep is necessary .... good health.",
      "options":[
        "for",
        "from",
        "of"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"Try .... as many languages as possible.",
      "options":[
        "learnt",
        "to learn",
        "learning"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"It is not easy .... all people",
      "options":[
        "please",
        "to be pleased",
        "to please"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Suganya is not capable of .... hard work.",
      "options":[
        "doing",
        "to be done",
        "do"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"I remember .... you last year.",
      "options":[
        "meet",
        "meeting",
        "to meet"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"I want the book .... in a week.",
      "options":[
        "writes",
        "written",
        "was written"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"The girls became .... on seeing the eclipse.",
      "options":[
        "excite",
        "excited",
        "exciting"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"Please get ....",
      "options":[
        "lost",
        "losing",
        "lose"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"My father will retire from service .... a year.",
      "options":[
        "in",
        "on",
        "by"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"Most of us eat .... a spoon.",
      "options":[
        "by",
        "for",
        "with"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Prasanna would have reached Bangalore by this time.",
      "options":[
        "present perfect",
        "past perfect",
        "future perfect"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Mahatma Gandhi was born in Porbandar.",
      "options":[
        "simple past",
        "simple future",
        "past continuous"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"My uncle has invested a lot of money .... farming.",
      "options":[
        "in",
        "for",
        "into"
      ],
      "correct":0
    },
    {
      "question":"New York is .... large city",
      "options":[
        "the",
        "a",
        "an"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"She wants to become .... engineer",
      "options":[
        "a",
        "the",
        "an"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Woman",
      "options":[
        "womens",
        "women",
        "womans"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"My sister cooks",
      "options":[
        "rise",
        "rice",
        "raise"
      ],
      "correct":1
    },
    {
      "question":"Loss",
      "options":[
        "loss",
        "loses",
        "losses"
      ],
      "correct":2
    },
    {
      "question":"Don't stand .... a tree when there is a lightning.",
      "options":[
        "under",
        "over",
        "below"
      ],
      "correct":0
    }
  ]
}